Hallelujah.
Amen. So, welcome to church. For those
that are visiting us, my name is Pastor
Tim Wangi. I want to begin today by
talking about uh the battle. The battle.
The battle. Mind battles. Mind battles.
Mind battles. I have around uh 45
minutes of a preacher. Tell your
neighbor of a preacher is not the one on
your watch. Uh but this one will be good
because pastor Rashid needs to have his
um
afternoon service.
Who finds you find in prayer now you
need money. Hallelujah. Amen. So those
that are getting married please let let
us not pray for them. They have prayed.
Give them money at this hour their
prayer item is they already know this is
the wife and this is the manonga.
Give them money. Tell your neighbor
neighbor when you are put on that
WhatsApp group don't be an intercessor.
Now become a facilitator.
Amen. That is done. Amen. and be ready
for many weddings because this is a
young church. So I'm ready. I have
around 17 messages. So I'm waiting for
weddings.
So let's get to the topic of the day.
Mind battles. Mind battles. Mind battle.
The reason why I call this mind battles
and not the battle of the mind is
because the battle of the mind is one of
the battles. There is the battle of the
mind and the battle to the mind. Those
are two different battles. Your mind can
become a battlefield and the devil likes
it that way. Your mind can become a
battlefield.
But let's begin with basic as we build
up. The first thing we need to
understand is that man is a triune
being. Man is a triune. That name triune
comes from the word trinity. And the
name trinity is not in the Bible. It is
a theological name that was coiled to
try to explain the mystery of the
godhead. That he's the father, the son,
and the holy spirit at the same time.
Yet he's still one. You can't explain
that in grammar. That is spiritual
language. It is a language in that
realm. In our realm, we can only coil a
word and call it trinity. Are we
together? So God, God is a triune
entity. He is three in one. He is one
that can be three and he's three that is
also one. Mystery.
NOW MAN [screaming]
IS ALSO A TRIUNE BEING. You also exist
in three facets. You have a body, you
have a soul and you have a spirit. So
man exist in three facets. You have
number one body, number two soul, number
three spirit. Now out of biological
studies, we have studied the body. It is
called in medical language they call it
the anatomy of the flesh. That is the
first course you do when you go to
nursing school or any good medical
school. You study the body from head to
toe. It is called the anatomy. You study
the brains, YOU STUDY THE HEART, YOU
STUDY the liver, the kidney. ALL THESE
THINGS WE can see them. The intestines,
the small, the big, the hand, the toe.
So that's the body. Are we together? SO
THAT IS THE ELEMENT WE SEE. AND BECAUSE
OF THE VISIBILITY OF THE BODY, MAN HAS
INVESTED A LOT IN THE BODY. We buy
designer clothes, designer perfumes, we
try to put makeup, MASCARA, EYELASHES,
ALL THESE THINGS JUST TO make the body
look good. BUT ALLOW ME TO TELL YOU, YOU
ARE NOT YOUR BODY. You are not the body.
YOU ARE A SPIRIT THAT LIVES IN A BODY.
SO WE HAVE INVESTED IN THE WRONG entity
and WE HAVE BEEN VERY LOUD TOWARDS THE
WRONG ENTITY. The real you is not the
one I'm SEEING HERE TODAY. TALL, DARK
AND HANDSOME. THOSE ARE THE PARAMETERS
OF YOUR DESCRIPTION. BUT THE REAL YOU IS
A SPIRIT. THE BODY IS LIKE A CAR THAT
CARRIES YOU. SO I CAN NEVER RELATE WITH
YOU ACCORDING TO THE SIZE OF YOUR BODY.
You can be big and useless and you can
be small and useful. SO IT IS NOT HOW
BIG YOU ARE. YOU CAN BE big and all you
do is occupy space because you ARE
MATTER BUT THERE IS NO RELEVANCE OF
LIFE. AND YOU CAN BE SMALL AND THE ONLY
THING YOU DO IS BREATHE OXYGEN AND DIE.
THAT CANNOT BE YOUR PORTION. AND THE
WORLD IS VERY LOUD ABOUT PHYSICALITY.
THIS IS WHERE SOCIALITES FIND THEIR
CAREER BECAUSE IT IS THE EXTERNALITY OF
SOME PARAMETERS for the lack of a better
word. That is what THEY KEEP ON SHOWING
US ON SOCIAL MEDIA. SO SOME PEOPLE HAVE
FOUND A CAREER ON HOW THEY ADDRESS THEIR
BODY. JESUS,
am I stepping on your toes, my man? IT
IS A FACT. PEOPLE HAVE GONE TO THE GYM
TO WORK ON THE BODY TO GET six packs,
biceps, and they don't know life is run
by concepts. AH
SO HAVE YOU REALIZED EVERYONE IS RUNNING
IN THE MORNING BECAUSE THEY ARE THEY
AWARE OF HEALTH. PEOPLE ARE EATING
HEALTHY. LISTEN AND HAVE NO PROBLEM. Eat
healthy but let me TELL YOU YOU ARE
HEALTH CUTS ACROSS. YOU NEED physical
you need soloulish AND SPIRITUAL HEALTH
FOR YOU to be healthy. YOU CAN BE HELD
PHYSIQUE BUT YOU ARE DYING [music] OF
DEPRESSION. YOU CAN BE HEALTHY EVEN IN
THE SOUL BUT SPIRITUALLY NO
RELATIONSHIP. SO THE BODY IS A GADGET
THAT CARRIES YOU.
THE BODY IS WHAT GIVES YOU LEGAL GROUND
TO OPERATE ON EARTH. WITHOUT A BODY YOU
ARE ILLEGAL on earth. SO THIS BODY IS
NOT ME. THIS is flesh and this flesh is
dirt.
Let's turn in the Bible now.
Let's begin by Genesis 1 because I want
to show and I might take time today just
to show you that you're a body, soul and
spirit. And then we look at the
components of the soul. Then next Sunday
we begin the journey of the battles of
the mind. Are we together? You need to
know you. Hello. WE DON'T DEAL WITH MEN
ACCORDING TO THE FLESH. YOU COULD BE
TALL, DARK, AND HANDSOME, BUT YOU HAVE A
BAD HEART.
Let's begin by Genesis 1:26.
Genesis 126. And we are not surgeons but
you have a bad heart. You are
unapproachable.
Some of you the problem is not prayer.
The reason why you are single is BECAUSE
IT IS NOT APPEARANCE. YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL
BUT ATTITUDE. Jesus attitude.
THAT ONE YOU CAN'T FIX IT BY PRAYER. WE
MUST ALIGN THE SOUL.
YOU HAVE FACE VALUE. YOU KNOW I'M
PREPARING FOR we have a meeting with a
young adults the fort and I'm working on
something and yesterday I was meditating
you know there are things you meditate
and say that's a good one and I
discovered this is this is a leakage I
discovered
beauty is for attention
BUT WHEN THE HEART is right I will
declare my intention
seller before I download that message.
IT IS SOMEWHERE IN MY SPIRITUAL ARCHIVES
WAITING FOR that day. So there are many
PEOPLE ALL THEY DO IS ATTRACT BUT NO ONE
HAS DECLARED INTENTION BECAUSE BEYOND
FACE VALUE there is no heart value.
Okay. Some of you after that message you
will get married quickly.
It will BE A SOLUTION.
THEN GOD SAID SO THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
IN FACT, WE CAN BEGIN FROM 26 25 there.
And and God made the beast of the earth.
Everybody read.
Uhhuh.
That's a very good area TO BEGIN. AND
GOD SAW THAT IT WAS GOOD. THAT NAME good
there MEANS FUNCTIONAL. SO EVERY animal
was made according to its kind. Its
kind. the beast of the the the beasts of
the beast of the earth TO ITS KIND,
CATTLE TO ITS KIND, BUT THERE WAS THE
creator did not have his kind.
SO GOD CREATED ANIMALS THAT carried
their kind. AND IN THE CONCLUSION OF
CREATION, THE CREATOR wanted to also
create something that has its kind.
Now you'll understand 126.
Who who is there? Yes. Don't write notes
AS I PREACH. THEN GOD SAID, "LET US MAKE
MAN in our PSALM." THE ORIGINAL VERSION.
YOU SEE THAT NAME MAN THERE? IT IS NOT
MAN HUMAN. IT IS MANKIND. THAT IS THE
RIGHT RENDERING OF THAT MAN. HE SAID,
"LET US MAKE MANKIND." A KIND OF US THAT
IS MAN. WE HAVE MADE CATTLE KIND. WE
HAVE MADE BEAST KIND BUT US IN THE GOD
LEVEL WE DON'T HAVE A KIND OF US. SO HE
SAID LET US MAKE A MANKIND. SO WHEN A
MAN CALLS YOU MANKIND THAT IS THE
ORIGINAL NAME OF CREATION BECAUSE YOU
ARE A MAN BUT A KIND OF GOD.
SO THAT'S WHY THE CONCEPT OF IMAGE it
was the REFLECTION AND THE AND THE AND
THE MANIFESTATION OF THE NATURE OF THAT
KIND.
ACCORDING TO OUR LIKENESS, ATTRIBUTES,
CHARACTER. BECAUSE EVERY ANIMAL GAVE
ACCORDING TO ITS KIND. SO IF A COW GAVE
BIRTH TO ANOTHER COW, IT MUST HAVE THE
LIKENESS OF A COW, IT MUST HAVE THE HEAD
AND THE FOUR LEGS. IF A BIRD GAVE TO ITS
KIND, IT MUST HAVE WINGS. SO WHEN GOD
GAVE TO HIS KIND, THERE ARE THINGS IN
GOD THAT MUST BE NEW NATURALLY BY
CREATION BECAUSE YOU ARE A KIND OF GOD.
THAT'S WHY THE PSALIST WRITES AND SAYS,
"DON'T YE KNOW THAT YE ARE GODS IN SMALL
G BECAUSE YOU ARE A KIND OF GOD."
AH, OKAY. It looks very HARD. I'M NOT
BLASPHEMING. I AM PREACHING SCRIPTURE. I
KNOW YOU ARE TAUGHT YOU ARE A NOBODY.
THAT IS A LEVEL OF PREACHING WHEN WE
WANT YOU TO be guilty OF YOUR SIN. BUT
THERE IS A LEVEL YOU ENTER WHERE YOU ARE
NOT DEALING WITH SIN. YOU ARE NOW
DEALING WITH GOD AS A SAINT. THE PROBLEM
IS THAT THE CHURCH IS STILL AS A SIN
LEVEL. SO WE CANNOT RELEASE SAINT
MYSTERIES. WE MUST STILL RELEASE SOME
SOME DOSES OF THE FLESH. DOSES ARE
FLESH. OH FAST BOY. THOSE ARE FLESH
DOSES. THERE IS A LEVEL YOU ENTER. I
WRITE TO THE SAINTS. I WRITE TO THE
SAINTS. THAT NAME SAINT MEANS HAGIOS.
THE HOLY ONES. THE SET AART ONES, THESE
ONES ARE NOT CONTAMINATED IN THE WORLD.
THESE ONES ARE NOW IN THE RADARS OF GOD.
THEY CAN MANIFEST GOD.
SAINTTHOOD YOU DON'T ACHIEVE WHEN YOU
DIE. SO THAT WE COME AND SAY WE HAVE
PRAYED THROUGH ANTHONY AND OUR PRAYERS
ARE ANSWERED AND THEN WE HAVE A
CORONATION DAY. THAT'S FOR ANOTHER
RELIGION. HERE WE ARE breathing living
saints sanctified, JUSTIFIED, SET APART.
NO APPETITE FOR THE WORLD GOING TO
HEAVEN, dealing and expressing the
natures of our kind.
AH LET US MAKE MAN IN OUR IMAGE
ACCORDING TO OUR LIKENESS. LET THEM HAVE
DOMINION OVER the fish. You can see the
word them. And then let's go to 27. This
is what this is the reason of your
creation. Okay, just stay there. This is
the reason of your creation. This is why
God CREATED MAN. THE WORD THEIR LETTERS
THE ELEMENT of God in plural plurality
in Hebrew it is a description of a big
being. So when Hebrew language when they
ARE WRITING IN HEBREW TO TALK ABOUT A
BIG PERSON LIKE THE president they might
use the word plural and the and and they
came but it's one man because they are
describing a big entity. HALLELUJAH. SO
THAT ONE DOES NOT MEAN MANY PEOPLE USED
TO SAY that
Listen,
GOD IS ONE. THERE'S ONLY ONE GOD.
THERE'S ONLY ONE GOD. AND THAT'S WHY I
BEGAN BY SAYING YOU ARE A TRIUNE MAN.
YOU HAVE A SPIRIT, A SOUL AND A BODY.
You are not three people. SO THE MOMENT
you look at yourself, YOU CARRY A
DIMENSION OF GOD OF TRINITY. AND YOUR
MEMBERS MUST WORK TOGETHER. YOUR SPIRIT,
YOUR SOUL AND YOUR BODY. BUT THERE ARE
TIMES WHEN YOUR BODY NEEDS TO WORK WHEN
THE SPIRIT CANNOT WORK. But there ARE
TIMES THE SPIRIT HAS TO WORK AND THERE
ARE TIME YOUR SOUL HAS TO WORK. IT
DOESN'T MAKE you three.
Uh am I speaking to anyone? SO NOW SO
THIS IS THE ESSENCE OF your life.
Dominion over the fish of the sea over
BS of the air over a cattle. THIS HAS
NOTHING TO TELL YOU THAT now you need to
be a fish farmer and chicken farmer AND
COW FARMER. THAT IS NOT DOMINION. THAT
IS what we call agriculture. THESE ARE
THE SPIRITUAL TERRAINS OF OPERATION.
WHERE DO BIRDS OPERATE FROM? THE AIR.
WHERE DO FISH OPERATE FROM? THE WATER.
WHERE DO CATTLE OPERATE FROM? THE
GROUND. SO YOU ARE GIVEN DOMINION OVER
AIR, THE THE WATER AND the ground. These
are the demonic territories. And these
are the territories. You ought to have
dominion. You have to have DOMINION IN
THE AIR WAVES. HAVE DOMINION on the
ground. HAVE DOMINION UNDER THE MARINE
POWER and the sea creature.
DOMINION. THE WORD TO DOMINATE MEANS
THEY ARE NOT ruling and overruling you.
It means THEY ARE UNDER YOUR AUTHORITY
AND POWER. SO IF MAN DOES NOT HAVE
DOMINION, HE IS A FAILURE according to
creation.
Okay.
The book of Genesis is full of metaphor.
If you understand English metaphor,
these are things that have hidden
meaning. I bless God because of the time
we are living. Men are at least people
have read. So now we can decode some
heavy stuff. You are not in the
generation of my mother whereby they
used to be told
Jehovah
COMMUNICATION COMMUNICATE. YOU KNOW
THAT'S HOW OUR MOTHERS WERE TAUGHT.
Tell your neighbor neighbor where your
motherunication.
NO THAT'S NOT YOUR LEVEL.
DEEP. [laughter]
AMEN.
So we must journey and that's why your
battles are deep. So
Amen. I've remembered my village pastor.
He will take 30 minutes to repeat the
SAME THING. SO GOD CREATED MAN singular
in his own image in the image of God. He
created him male and female. He created.
Now go to 26. Let me tell you something.
You see the moment man does not have
dominion. The moment you are not
dominating
automatically it means something else is
dominating you THE WHAT WE CALL
DEPRESSION IS WHAT I CALL DEEP
OPPRESSION. MEANING THAT SOMETHING HAS
OPPRESSED YOU AND YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO
OVERRULE IT. SO BECAUSE YOUR NATURE IS
NOT TO BE RULED BUT TO RULE. NOW THAT
YOU ARE UNDER RULERSHIP, YOU ARE
OPERATING against your nature AND THAT'S
WHAT MEN CALL DEPRESSION.
THEN NOW SOMETHING HAS TAKEN OVER WHERE
YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO TAKE OVER AND WE
SHALL COME TO THAT NOT FROM A MENTAL
AWARENESS HELD WEEK. NO, WE WILL COME
FROM scripture and begin to show you how
man begins to dominate over matters that
have dominated him because YOU ARE A
TOOL OF DOMINION.
HALLELUJAH. YOU ARE A TOOL of dominion.
So now look at 27. This is the man GOD
CREATED. SO THE IDEA OF GOD MAKING MAN,
MANKIND, A KIND OF MAN THAT IS LIKE GOD
CAME FROM THE FATHER. SO YOUR IDEA OF
EXISTENCE IS NOT A PRODUCT OF YOUR
PARENTS STATE. DON'T THINK THAT IT WAS
OOPS. NO, YOU ARE NOT AN oops baby.
No, NO, NO. LET THEM NEVER TELL YOU
THAT WAS NOT THEIR DESIGN. ALL THE DAYS
WRITTEN in your book, oh God, were
written before EVEN A MEMBER OF MY BODY
WAS FORMED IN THE WOMB OF MY MOTHER.
MEANING THAT I SHOWED UP IN MY MOTHER'S
WOMB AT THE RIGHT TIME BECAUSE UNTIL YOU
UNDERSTAND WHETHER YOU ARE FATHER AND
MOTHER STILL MARRIED MAYBE THEIR core
business was to bring YOU FORTH
RELATIONSHIP WAS NOT THE AGENDA IT'S you
are YOU GETTING ME SO SO DON'T BEGIN TO
FEEL LIKE OH YOU KNOW
LISTEN THE MOMENT YOU TAKE THE LANGUAGE
of you as an idea of God, you kill the
concept of purpose.
AND I'LL SAY THIS, THE CURRENT TEACHING
ABOUT EVOLUTION IS WHERE THEY SAY SOME
MOLECULES CAME TOGETHER. SO THOSE
MOLECULES ARE ACCIDENTAL. AND THAT'S WHY
THAT CONVERSATION AUTOMATICALLY TAKES
men out OF PURPOSE BECAUSE PURPOSE TELLS
ME I WAS I'M HERE FOR A REASON. I'M HERE
FOR A SEASON AND IT is only God who can
CONFIRM IT. SO WHEN I BECOME A BUNCH OF
CELLS THAT [music] ARE LIVING AND THEN
AFTER THAT DISINTEGRATE, THERE IS NO
REASON OF MY BEING, I'LL BECOME ANYTHING
THAT LIFE OFFERS. SO I NEED TO AFFIRM TO
YOU, YOU ARE HERE BY DIVINE DESIGN. I
SAY YOU ARE HERE BY DIVINE DESIGN.
WHETHER YOUR MOM WAS AN ALCOHOL BREWER,
WHETHER YOUR MOM WAS A WAS A PROSTITUTE
AND YOU'VE NEVER MET YOUR DAD, THE ISSUE
IS ACCORDING to the CALENDAR OF HEAVEN,
YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO SHOW UP NOW. HOW YOU
CAME IS NOT THE ISSUE. THE ISSUE IS YOU
ARE HERE AND THE DEVIL is in trouble.
PERIOD. SO GOD CREATED MAN IN HIS OWN
IMAGE, IN THE IMAGE of God. He created
him. NOW YOU CAN SEE singularity man.
This one is not male. MAN, MAN. THAT
WORD IS MANKIND.
SO GOD CREATED A KIND OF HIMSELF THAT IS
MAN. AND THAT KIND CARRIED TWO
DIMENSIONS. HE CARRIED MALE DIMENSION
AND FEMALE DIMENSION. THIS ONE IS NOT
GENDER IS DIMENSION. SOMEBODY SAY
DIMENSION.
GENDER IS A PRODUCT OF YOUR SEXUAL ORGAN
PLACEMENT. That's gender.
That's why we say this is a MAN BECAUSE
WE CALL YOU A MAN FROM SEXUAL organ
dimension. But this one is A LANGUAGE OF
HEAVEN. GOD DOES NOT HAVE SEXUAL ORGANS.
IT'S HEATHEN GODS THAT MARRY. HE GODS.
THOSE ONES MARRY. THOSE ARE STRANGE
GODS. THEY EVEN HAVE CHILDREN WHO DIED
AND THEY DIED. THOSE ARE strange gods.
[snorts]
They have grandfathers and grandmothers
and you know religion is very bad
because you you you you believe in a god
that was buried and you believe okay
let's stick here
now so so GOD DOES NOT HAVE GENDER okay
there's no female or male the language
of male and female is dimension male
represents authority female represents
power that's
Men represents authority. So don't think
I KNOW WE DRAW MAN FROM masculinity with
beards and all these things. Let us not
be fooled. Angels have no gender. They
have a form but they have no gender. We
don't have sleigh queen angels. So stop
calling these people angels.
Hallelujah.
BECAUSE THEY NEVER MARRY NOR BUT THE
DESCRIPTION OF COURSE IS ALWAYS
MASCULINE BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY MALE
REPRESENTS AUTHORITY FEMALE represents
power. SO WHAT WAS GOD CREATING? A KIND
THAT HAS AUTHORITY and power.
MALE AND FEMALE AUTHORITY AND POWER. HE
CREATED THEM. THE FIRST MAN WHO WAS A
KIND OF GOD WAS A COMBINATION OF POWER
AND AUTHORITY LIVING in an entity, a
spirit. THIS MAN WAS NOT A PHYSICAL MAN.
THIS ONE WAS A SPIRIT. HE WAS IN THE
LEVEL OF GOD.
THIS ONE,
THAT'S WHY THIS MAN WAS created
because there is a created man. Everyone
is a created man. And that is THE
ORIGINAL MAN. WHAT is to create is to
bring into existence out of nothing.
That is creation. Bringing into
existence out of nothing. Like this
church was created because it has never
existed. We just sat down began to saw a
few things and we brought it up. This
guy whatever is playing right now these
are new tunes. They have never been
played. He's creating sound.
He's not duplicating. He's creating he
HE'S TAPPING SOMETHING THAT HAS NEVER
EXISTED. AND CAUSING IT TO MANIFEST.
THAT'S HOW man was created. SO THE FIRST
MAN WAS A SPIRIT MAN. HELLO. Tell your
neighbor, neighbor. AND THAT'S WHO YOU
ARE. YOU ARE A SPIRIT. ARE WE TOGETHER?
YOU ARE A SPIRIT. BUT WE HAVE INVESTED A
LOT IN THE FLESH.
NOW LET'S JOURNEY AND begin to study
this man. Genesis 2:7.
To some of you, this is a recap.
Everybody read. God.
Read it well. GOD FORMED MAN OUT OF DIRT
FROM THE ground and blew into his
nostril the breath of life. THE MAN CAME
ALIVE a living soul seller. Let's begin
FROM THERE. SO THERE IS A GOD SAID LET
US make man MAKE THEN GOD CREATED.
THIS IS THE FIRST CLASS YOU ATTEND in
theology is called English 101
so that you can understand language
grammar. NOW THIS IS GRAMMAR. THERE IS A
CREATED MAN and a formed man.
So you NEED TO UNDERSTAND THERE IS A MAN
IN YOU THAT IS FORMED AND A MAN IN YOU
THAT IS CREATED. I know we call this
scripture IN JEREMIAH 15. BEFORE I
FORMED THEE, I KNEW THEE. So who DID GOD
KNOW? NOT THE FORM BUT THE CREATED
ENTITY.
BECAUSE JEREMIAH IN THE SPIRIT WAS A
PROPHET BEFORE HE APPEARED IN A FORM.
BEFORE I FORMED THEE, I KNEW THEE. I
ANOINTED THEE, I ORDAINED THEE, JESUS,
THE MAN CAME AS A PROPHET. AS HE WAS
CRYING, GOD SAW A PROPHET, NOT A YOUNG
CHILD SUCKLING. BECAUSE THE ORDINATION
DID NOT WAIT FOR A DAY WITH MEN WITH
ROBES AND A HORN. THE MAN WHO WAS
FASHIONED AS A PROPHET IN THE BEFORE.
WHAT IS THAT? BEFORE YOU EXISTED as a
spiritual force before you came as
matter.
This is the physical. I KNOW SOME OF YOU
EVEN ARE NOT BELIEVING WHAT I'M SAYING
BECAUSE YOU THINK YOU BEGAN TO LIVE WHEN
YOU ARE BORN. THAT IS THE TIME THE FORM
STEPPED IN.
YOU ARE IN GOD. YOU ARE IN ETERNITY WITH
GOD WAITING FOR THE TIME OF YOUR SHOWING
FORTH.
And that's why in the fullness of time
you'll go back where you came from.
Hallelujah. Am I speaking to anyone? Am
I speaking to anyone? SO, SO LET THE
FORM NOT LIMIT YOU. [music] I CAN DWELL
THERE. MANY HAVE been entrapped in this
flesh. They have been limited in this
flesh. MANY HAVE NEVER STEPPED out of
the flesh. And the realities and the
blessings of Zion are not in the flesh,
they are in the spirit. So God formed
man out of that. SO
that that is that
brown skin, black skin, TALL, DARK AND
HANDSOME. TALL DARK MTOP HANDSOME IS
PERSONAL.
Tell your neighbor neighbor.
COME ON. HEAVEN WHEN THE ECONOMY WAS
GOOD AND YOU FOUND THERE WAS MORE MTOPE.
IT IS GOOD. We can call you big and
[music] fat. You just came in the right
time of the economy.
It is good. We can CALL YOU SMALL BUT
YOU JUST SHOWED UP IN the wrong time of
THE ECONOMY. BUT
AND I CAN PROVE TO YOU IF YOU close all
these doors and we stay here for a month
and we die decompose. Guess what to
heaps of soil and bones to to
that's who you are. YOU CAN IMAGINE HOW
YOU HAVE TAKEN CARE OF THIS MTOPE. YOU
YOU YOU BUY DESIGNER PERFUME FOR MTOPE.
YOU BUY UH BRAZILIAN WEAVE 25,000 MINUS
TAX FOR MTOPE. YOU BUY MASCARA, PUT FAKE
BOOTS, YOU KNOW, FOR A JESUS.
One pack,
tell your neighbor, neighbor.
AND I TELL YOU, MEN [screaming] HAVE
INVESTED.
IF IN FACT WHATEVER WE CALL FOUNDATION,
all these things we play on our face, it
is modified soil
mata vi. And we
And we call it makeup.
Jesus.
Oh. Oh. O ladies, I'm sorry.
But we are having a conversation.
Hallelujah. SO YOU CAN IMAGINE HOW WE
HAVE INVESTED BECAUSE ALL WE KNOW IS
THAT WE ARE A BODY. BUT MANY OF US IN
THE REALM OF THE SPIRIT, WE ARE SO UGLY.
NO MAKEUP, NO NOTHING, no stamina, no
capacity. AND THE FLESH, THE FLESH WILL
COME WITH FOUR THINGS. THE FLESH WILL
COME WITH DESIRES. The flesh will come
WITH PASSIONS. THE FLESH WILL COME WITH
LUST. AND THE flesh will come with
appetites. Four things. Desires,
PASSIONS, LUST, AND APPETITE.
SO WHY DID GOD GIVE YOU A FLESH? IT WILL
COME WITH DESIRES, PASSION, LUST, and
appetite. AND AND GOD GAVE YOU THE FLESH
TO GIVE YOU legal ground on earth. NOW
REMEMBER, THE FLESH CAME FROM THE
GROUND. [snorts] THE FLESH WILL NEVER
LEAD YOU TO GOD. Everything has a
source. THE SPIRIT CAME FROM THE FATHER,
BUT THE FLESH CAME FROM THE GROUND. THE
MOMENT YOU FOLLOW THE FLESH, IT will
always take you to THE WORLD. THE MOMENT
YOU FOLLOW THE SPIRIT, IT WILL ALWAYS
connect you TO THE SOURCE. THAT IS WHY
THERE IS A BATTLE BETWEEN THE FLESH AND
WHERE IT CAME FROM AND BETWEEN THE
SPIRIT AND WHERE it came from. AND THESE
ARE LIKE TWO ANIMALS IN YOUR LIFE. YOU
HAVE A FLESH, YOU FEED THE FLESH MORE,
THE spirit will be disempowered. You
feed the SPIRIT MORE, THE FLESH WILL be
disempowered. It's like you have two
dogs, white and black. The black one is
the flesh and the white one is the
spirit. The one you feed more will rule.
Are we together? The flesh is not evil.
The flesh is not bad. IS BECAUSE EVEN
THE PASSIONS, DESIRES, LUST AND
APPETITES, SOME OF THESE THINGS ARE NOT
WICKED.
I TELL YOU, IT'S ONLY THAT THEY ARE
HIJACKED BY THE ENEMY.
AND SO THAT'S WHY GOD CANNOT TAKE OUT
THE FLESH. GOD WILL GIVE YOU THE SPIRIT
FOR SELF-CONTROL. THAT'S HOW YOU YOU
GOVERN THE FLESH. YOU MANAGE THE FLESH.
JESUS. BEING BORN AGAIN DOES NOT TAKE
AWAY SEXUAL DESIRES. Are we together?
AND LET NO ONE LIE TO YOU. COLD WATER
DOES NOT take away sexual desires. IT IS
NOT A HYGIENE ISSUE.
WE HAVE LIED TO CHURCH.
I TELL YOU PEOPLE TAKE SHOWERS AND STILL
COME BACK SAYING LISTEN
YOU NEED THE GOVERNANCE OF THE HOLY
GHOST.
OKAY.
NO, you need the shower OF THE WORD.
WASH THY MIND WITH THE WORD OF GOD. AND
THEN THE HOLY GHOST WILL GIVE YOU
SELF-CONTROL. WHAT DOES SELF-CONTROL
MEAN? It means management and
governance. There are things I want TO
GO FOR, BUT I'M TRYING TO HOLD MYSELF
AND I CAN'T DO IT BY MY STRONG WILL. I
NEED A STRONGER POWER THAN THE POWER THE
FLESH IS MANIFESTING. It is LIKE WHEN
YOU HAVE A DOG ON A LEASH. YOU SEE THE
STRENGTH OF THE LEASH THAT CUMBER CAN
CONTROL A 150 bulldog kg depending WITH
THE STRENGTH. SOME OF US OUR FLESH IS
LIKE THE DOG. ONE DAY I WAS GOING
through an estate of rich foxes mothiga
AND I SAW A BULLDOG VERY UGLY and the
bulldog looked at me and I looked at it
and I ignored it then I looked at it and
it was still looking at me AND YOU KNOW
BULLDOGS DON'T CLOSE THEIR MOUTH THEY
THEY POURING A LOT OF SURVIVOR THEN THE
DOG BEGAN TO B AND I SAW THE MAN BEHIND
THE DOG WAS A SLIM GUY [snorts] BUT
THERE WAS A STRONG METALLIC UH KIND OF
LEASH AND THE DOG STOOD ON HIS LEGS
WANTING TO JUMP AND THE MAN STRUGGLED
AND THE HOLY GHOST revealed to me and he
told me that's how I deal with your
flesh. The spirit is like the man. HE
MIGHT LOOK SMALL THEN the the leash is
the control that THE SPIRIT OFFERS. NO
MATTER HOW HEAVY YOUR FLESH IS, THERE
ARE TIMES
relationship
after two days.
Tell your neighbor neighbor that's why
we need the Holy Ghost because it takes
the [music] spirit to contain the flesh.
WE CAN'T RUN AWAY FROM THE FLESH. BUT
GOD HAD AN IDEA WITH THE FLESH. He
created the flesh [music] to give you
access on earth. Because the assignment
of man is NOT IN HEAVEN. HEAVEN WE ARE
GOING FOR REWARD. THERE IS A SEAT IN
HEAVEN called the beamer seat. The bema
SEAT IS LIKE WHERE RIGHT NOW WE HAVE
OLYMPICS. WHEN YOU WIN THERE IS a place
where they stand and they GIVEN THE
MEDALS. THAT IS THAT BEAMER SEAT IS A
CORINTHIAN WORD OF A PLACE WHERE A
CHAMPION stood to RECEIVE MEDALS. NOW
BELIEVERS WILL FACE CHRIST ON THE BEAMER
SEAT. IT'S CALLED THE MEDAL GIVING SEAT.
WHY? BECAUSE HERE THEY CONQUERED. AND
ONE OF THE BATTLES YOU HAVE TO WIN IS
THAT OF THE FLESH. That's why Paul wrote
and said, "I crucify my FLESH DAILY."
IT'S NOT A ONE DAY AFFAIR. AS YOU WAKE
UP, YOU SAY, "I DIE. I'm living, but I'm
dying. It's no LONGER ME WHO LIVES, BUT
CHRIST IN ME." THIS IS THE ONLY WAY to
walk pure. HALLELUJAH. YOU MUST HAVE THE
CAPACITY BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T CONTROL
THE FLESH, THE FLESH WILL CONTROL YOU.
THE FLESH WILL NEVER take you to church.
[snorts]
Jesus is Lord.
Tell your neighbor the flesh is not bad.
If you don't understand its use, you'll
abuse it. Are we together? The flesh has
a work and that is to bring to introduce
you into the earth for assignment.
Without this flesh, we are useless
because spirits can never work. Can I go
even deeper? Now, the Holy Ghost needs
the flesh to express the realities of
God.
The spirit of God cannot operate without
the flesh. You can see this order in
creation. This is WHAT GOD DID. HE
CREATED THE FLESH of Christ.
It was born. It was raised. WHEN THE
FLESH WAS READY, THE HOLY GHOST came and
dwelt IN THE FLESH. AND AFTER THAT,
THAT'S WHEN THE MINISTRY, THE ASSIGNMENT
OF CHRIST BEGAN AFTER AFTER JORDAN. WHEN
THE HOLY GHOST CAME AND FOUND A VESSEL
TO PARTNER WITH, even in this world, IT
IS A BATTLE OF VESSELS. THE DEVIL IS
LOOKING FOR BODIES. WHY THE DEVIL
UNDERSTANDS DEMONS CANNOT OPERATE ON
EARTH WITHOUT a body. So it is a battle
of bodies.
It's not a battle of anything. And
that's why now the soul comes in. The
soul comes in. Let me have three people.
That that's where the soul comes in.
Now let's assume this is the flesh. This
is all what we see. Okay. Okay. This is
the spirit. The spirit is always small,
malnourished.
And this is the soul. Are we together?
Now listen to me. The battle is a battle
of bodies. But you can never have access
to a body if you don't have control to a
soul. That's why we win souls. Are we
together now? Why? Why did God create a
soul? We see in this one. He blew into
his nostrils the breath of life. THEN
MAN CAME ALIVE, a living soul. Now allow
me to share something that a little bit
deep, but follow me quickly. THE REALITY
YOU DON'T SEE BECAUSE YOU HAVE EYEBALLS.
YOU DON'T HEAR BECAUSE YOU HAVE EARNS.
YOU DON'T TALK BECAUSE YOU HAVE A MOUTH
AND a tongue. NEITHER DO YOU DO ALL YOU
THINK and do because you have these
gadgets of the body. There is a
controller.
YOU HAVE EYES BUT SIGHT IS IN THE SOUL.
YOU HAVE A MOUTH BUT SPEECH IS IN THE
SOUL. YOU HAVE EARS BUT HEARING IS IN
THE SOUL. SO THE BODY GOD FORMED A BODY
BUT THIS BODY WAS USELESS. IT BECAME
ALIVE WHEN THE SOUL ENTERED IN that
body.
THAT IS WHY WHEN MEN DIE WE WE ARE LEFT
WITH MOUTH AND ALL THE ORGANS BUT THEY
CAN'T WORK BECAUSE THE THE SOUL HAS
EXITED THE SCENE. It is like I HAVE A
PHONE AND I PUT IT ON CHARGER FULL
BATTERY. THAT PHONE WILL OPERATE EVERY
SOFTWARE WORKING. THERE IS A LEVEL MY
PHONE REACHES AND TELLS ME BATTERY LOW
AND IT ASK FOR PERMISSION TO SHUT SOME
SOFTWARES AND WHEN I PRESS OKAY I CAN'T
ACCESS NETWORK. [music]
There are things that cannot happen. AND
IN MEDICAL SCIENCE THERE ARE TIMES THEY
BEGIN TO SAY YOU ARE medically dead.
OTHERWISE THE SOUL WAS DETACHED.
The heart is beating because there is
circulation and the heart IS BEING
HELPED BY THE MACHINE TO PUMP BLOOD. SO
IT'S CIRCULATING BUT THE SYSTEM DIED
LONG TIME AGO. SO THE SOUL IS WHAT GIVES
capacity
is what gives capacity. WHEN YOU GO TO
DEPTHS OF WITCHCRAFT, MEN ARE TRAINED
HOW TO MANIPULATE THE SOUL. THIS IS HOW
A MAN CAN LOOK AT YOU AND CLOSE THE
GATES of your eye AND YOU BECOME BLIND.
A MAN CAN LOOK AT YOU AND SHUT THE GATES
OF YOUR HEARING AND YOU BECOME DEAF. A
MAN CAN LOOK AT YOU AND ALTER AT YOUR
SOUL AND YOU BECOME MAD. It is the
economy of the soul. They have been
trained. They know it. They can journey
and
hallelujah. So this body is the most
useless thing on this this one. We keep
on boasting with it.
I had a roommate who was a mog attendant
when I was in campus. He used to come
for studies. I didn't have time to go
home. So I used to stay in campus and he
told me
and he told me that's the best job.
And he told me I've seen people and
after 3 days
you become so useless. This body is so
useless without the soul. Are you
getting me? And you can see how much we
have added value to the body. You can
see how social
next time you just look at them just
tell them this is a bunch of dirt.
Some of them concentrated in some arenas
of your life but you are just dust
cell.
This body is so useless.
The soul is what governs
the body. Now the spirit
this one cannot affect the body by
bypassing the soul. So the spirit must
communicate to the soul and the soul
must now communicate to the body. SO THE
BATTLES OF LIFE the devil CAN NEVER
ATTACK YOUR SPIRIT. It is twof. That's
why THE BIBLE SAYS FEAR HIM THAT HAS THE
POWER TO DESTROY BOTH THE FLESH AND THE
SPIRIT. It's only one. The devil can
never touch your spirit. HE CAN'T. THE
BATTLE OF THE DEVIL ENDS HERE. He can
deal with YOUR BODY [music] AND DEAL
with your soul. AND THE SOUL HAS THE
MIND. YOUR MIND IS IN YOUR SOUL. AND
[music] WE'LL COME TO THAT. THE BATTLES
OF JOB WERE physical flesh attack by
affliction and diseases. THE SECOND ONE
WAS THE THREE MEN PLUS THE WIFE THAT
SURROUNDED HIM ACCUSING HIM IN MORE THAN
10 CHAPTERS.
THIS WAS THE BATTLE FOR THE MIND. MEN
SPEAKING TO THE SOUL and [music]
speaking to you. Even the WIFE TELLING
HIM CAST GOD AND LEAVE. BUT GUESS WHAT?
THE RELATIONSHIP OF JOB WAS NOT IN THE
FLESH. IT was not in the soul. IT WAS IN
THE SPIRIT. AND THAT'S WHY THE EYES OF
THE SPIRIT SAW AND HE CONFESSED, "MY
REDEEMER LIVETH." BECAUSE THE
POSSIBILITIES OF THIS DIMENSION NEVER
HINDERED THE CONNECTION OF THE SPIRIT.
EVERY BATTLE IN YOUR LIFE, IT'S EITHER
IN THE soul depression or in the flesh
oppression. DISEASES ARE ALL HERE.
MENTAL ISSUES ARE HERE. SO WE CAN see
the devil has moved a notch higher in
attacking our time.
SO WE ARE NOT DEALING WITH ANYTHING.
THERE IS NOTHING NEW UNDER THE SUN. SO
WE DON'T NEED MENTAL HEALTH CLASSES. WE
NEED TO UNDERSTAND WHAT IS THIS SOUL?
WHAT DOES IT CARRY? BECAUSE THE MOMENT
THE DEVIL HAS CONTROL OF THE SOUL, HE
HAS CONTROL of the life. This soul WILL
BE SO OPPRESSED THAT it will tell the
body to hang itself
because the body is AT THE MASSES.
REMEMBER, SEE WHAT THE BIBLE SAYS, the
breath OF LIFE, THE MAN BECAME ALIVE, a
living soul. And some versions say a
living being. This is a being. Without a
soul, it is not living.
Am I speaking to anyone? Yes.
I'm introducing you to you.
It's my life. Now, let me tell you how
your life looks like. This is you. This
is the life you think you have. But this
is the reality of what controls your
life. Can I go deeper? Now, the moment
you're not born again, your spirit is
always dead. So, it's like you have no
spirit. This is a man who's not born
again. So this man relies on what he
feels and what he knows he's THAT'S WHY
THE CONCEPT of all this conversation
about um you know if you want to be
sexual orientation if you want to be
lesbian or gay do what you feel it is
the absence of a living spirit because
feelings and emotions are here and we
are pushing a generation to do what they
feel but assignment is in the spirit and
the moment you do what You feel AND YOU
DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT BEFORE I FORMED
THEE, YOU ARE A SPIRIT. I ordained thee.
If this reality does not manifest in
this flesh, you are a dualist and a
useless man on earth. You will do things
without fulfillment BECAUSE YOU ARE JUST
RUNNING LIFE.
AND THIS IS NOW THE GENERATION OF DO
WHAT YOU FEEL. IT IS THE GREATEST
PHILOSOPHY OF SATANISM. DO WHAT THOU
WILL. THAT IS THE BANNER. THAT IS THE
MOTO OF THE FREEMASON. IT IS THEIR MOTO.
THE WAY YOU GO TO A SCHOOL AND YOU SEE
BETTER YOUR BEST IS OUR MOTO. THE
FREEMASON MOTO IS DO WHAT THOU WILL.
MEANING THAT LET THE HOLY GHOST NEVER
GOVERN YOU. RELY ON THE WILLNESS OF this
dimension. And that's the generation we
are raising. You know you can be
anything. It doesn't matter.
You cannot be anything. You can be only
what God ordained you to be. THAT'S THE
REALITY. UNTIL YOU JOURNEY AND LOCATE
YOURSELF in the spirit, you might
survive on the shadows of other men and
become useless and die without
fulfilling anything. That's why you need
to know God for yourself and understand
who I am and begin to manifest who you
are as unique as you are and become. Can
I go deeper just to explain? This is
where you begin to see a man saying this
is a dead spirit. [music] So when you
have a dead spirit, you have only two
things. You have a soul and a body. The
devil is in need of bodies. So this is
why you hear a man saying, "I have sold
my soul to the devil." What does that
mean? The original thing what they do,
they don't take out a soul. You can't
take out this soul and sell it. You you
enter into contracts. The original word
for signature is a seal. And so in that
contract, you sign and as you sign, you
are placing your life on that document.
Even today if YOU ENTER A CONTRACT WITH
ME OF 50 million if you don't pay the
money your life is at stake in that
contract and what AUTHENTS
by taking it out and saying NO IT IS BY
APPENDING TO SOME documents and they say
they append it with their OWN BLOOD AND
AT THAT TIME YOU ARE YOU YOUR BODY
BECOMES OPEN TO demons and so you you
ARE AN ARTIST BUT NOW THE SPIRIT IS
DEAD. So demons now begin to use your
body for their own expression. SO THIS
IS AN ARTIST ON STAGE AND HE'S UNDER
CERTAIN DEMON. THE DEMON WILL TAKE
CHARGE of the flesh. HE WILL TATTOO ALL
HIS BODY. THE DEMON WILL TAKE CHARGE OF
THE FLESH. HE WILL PIERCE us all his
body. The demon WILL TAKE CHARGE OF THE
FLESH. BY THE TIME HE SHOWS UP ON STAGE,
HE'S NAKED. IT IS NOT FASHION. THERE IS
A DEMON SELLING AN AGENDA AND THEN THEY
WANT US TO CELEBRATE THEM. WE MUST be
wise.
This why we tell people secular music.
Some of the people have serious
covenants with demons. SO WHATEVER YOU
ARE LISTENING TO IS NOT THE ARTIST YOU
SEE ON TV. This is the body OF THE
ARTIST. THE SOUND HERE, HEY, is
depression.
So the way he's moving this one. SO YOU
YOU ARE CELEBRATING A FLESH BUT DEEP
DOWN THE FLESH IS UNDER CERTAIN BONDAGE.
By the time you realize
this spirit has an assignment,
by the time you listen to this song in
your house for 10 days, you don't pray.
Begin to dream having sex with strange
men. Why?
Okay.
Hello.
I miss you
group
in church. I just want to tell you I'm
in the raceway.
[snorts]
Tell your neighbor, neighbor,
be walk.
It's time to be wise. Are we together?
So we begin to see even demons know they
can't operate without a body. The battle
is not just for souls is also for bodies
because body gives you legal ground of
operation on earth. But you see this is
the controlling this is the control
room. So we need we need the soul.
That's why we win souls.
Have you ever wondered your why see we
are going for soul winning. You don't
even know what you're winning.
Seven souls came to the Lord. What were
those? SEVEN MEN AND WOMEN. NO THOSE ARE
BODIES OF MEN AND WOMEN. What did you
win?
[snorts] HOW DO YOU WIN A SOUL to the
Lord? How? THAT MEANS YOU ARE BRINGING
THAT SOUL TO THE COVENANTS of eternity.
AND THE ONLY PATHWAY IS BY THE HOLY
GHOST TO GET IN BY THE POWER OF
REGENERATION AND RESURRECTION TO RAISE A
DEAD SPIRIT BACK TO LIFE. AND WHEN THE
DEAD SPIRIT IS BACK TO LIFE, THE
REALITIES OF A LIVING spirit will begin
to influence this soul and the flesh
will change.
SO WE ARE DOING COUNSELING HERE but the
problem is here.
Oh you know you are depressed. So what
was your background like?
Oh Jesus. So you're from a single mother
that could be the root cause of your
depression. So self-esteem it's no
self-esteem. Listen those are
terminologies
in the secular world. You have a
spiritual rank problem. IT IS EITHER THE
spirit is so low that the flesh is so
high in desire
OR WHATEVER IS IN this soul is so
perverted that the expression is an
esteem. An esteem is a feeling. Now let
the Bible be the Bible. We are not
psychiatrist
and even psychiatrists come to a place
where they fail.
In fact, the law of psychology, you
counel around 15 people, you also go for
counseling.
That's the law. So, they are counselors
of counselors. I don't know where the
cycle ends. So, those who cancel
counselors, I don't know who cancel THE
COUNSELOR OF COUNSELORS. THAT'S WHY YOU
NEED THE HOLY GHOST. WHO IS THE mighty
counselor? MATTERS ARE SETTLED THERE.
DESIRES, ALIGNMENT, PROCLIVITY. He gives
you his desires. They are MORE SUICIDAL.
APPETITES are settled there.
Contentment.
There are days we used to breach fire
because the flesh was not ruling.
That was not the issue.
Revival meeting because it was not about
appearance. We were so lost in God that
what affects flesh never affected us.
That never defined us. It never gave us
status.
They called spiritual encounters
after seeing the glory because your
DESIRES HAVE SHIFTED. THE TANGENT is
eternal.
[snorts]
It was for eternal things and that's how
things follow you. But the moment
proclivities are here, Jesus, you will
need to keep clients in church.
Seven keys of becoming a millionaire.
Somebody say I'M A MILLIONAIRE. AND
PEOPLE ARE DYING IN POVERTY.
We may SHOUT I'M A MILLIONAIRE 50
TIMES,000.
You need to ask that.
IF THEY CAN'T WORK FOR HIM, HE HAS NO
BUSINESS PREACHING THEM.
The school of millionaires, the mindset
of a millionaire,
read those notes because even the
LOCATION WHERE YOU ARE DOING THAT
BROADCAST, I CAN TELL YOU HAVE NO
CAPACITY.
OKAY.
10 ways of become see.
Tell your neighbor neighbor the soul.
Tell your neighbor the mind
is in the soul.
This is what makes the body to be alive.
What we call death is the exit of the
soul [music] and the spirit.
Are we together? That's what we call
death physically. When this one exits is
like a phone that has been plugged out
of power in a matter of no time, it will
go off. And until you get power, I I
don't think dead men lose their eyes.
Some even die opening their eyes. They
still have eyeball but THEY CANNOT SEE.
MOUTH BUT THEY cannot talk because their
capacity of speech, sight, hearing was
in the soul. I'll give you a homework to
go and read at home
the story of the rich man and Lazarus.
Where was their encounter?
Not on earth. So the BIBLE SAYS THEY
DIED BOTH OF THEM. ONE WAS CARRIED BY AN
ANGEL. THE OTHER ONE WAS BURIED. That's
a very sad statement. A rich man that
was buried. A POOR MAN THAT was carried
by angels. Both of them died. SO THEY
ENTERED A SPIRITUAL REALM. BUT read that
story. Lazarus saw
the rich man heard. He felt pain. HE
SAID, "POUR some water on my tongue."
Not this one. It was what gave the
tongue power to taste and sense.
THAT CONVERSATION IS NOT ON EARTH. IT IS
OUTSIDE THE EARTH. AND THAT IS NOT A
CONVERSATION OF BODIES. It is a SOUL
CONVERSATION. NOW THE PROBLEM IS WHERE
THE SOUL GOES
is where the spirit will go.
And so the soul will create awareness to
the spirit.
Hallelujah.
And it IS THE SAME SOUL THAT WILL SAY TO
MY WE made it because the spirit
is also under the governance.
Now you see where the battle is now.
When a man is born again, God does not
need to use your soul to talk to you.
When a MAN IS BORN AGAIN, THE
INTERACTIONS OF God are in the spirit.
And then this spirit now [music] begins
to rule the soul. Now listen, this is
the life of an unbeliever. Face that
side face. This is the life of an
unbeliever. The first thing you'll meet
in an unbeliever is body, soul,
food.
Those are
unbelievers.
Now this
some of you this is how you come for
dates.
It was a game of body and emotions
and that's why the way you are
heartbroken the spirit was not there.
THAT'S WHY YOU TOOK TIME TO DRESS THIS
BODY in a sexy way.
July
and that's why the because what is in
the soul is so much of the world so it
influence how the body should appear.
So this is not a date. It is an
encounter of bodies. Nothing spiritual.
And then you keep on asking WHY IS IT
THAT ALL MEN ARE AFTER SEX. Listen you
brought body.
The thing has to reverse.
The thing HAS TO REVERSE. THAT THE FIRST
PERSON WE MEET IS THE YOU in the spirit.
THIS IS WHY PAUL WRITES AND SAYS, "NOW I
KNOW NO MAN AFTER THE FLESH BECAUSE THE
FIRST THING I ENCOUNTER IS THE DEALINGS
OF THE SPIRIT. THAT BY THE TIME I'M
SHOWING UP IN THAT GATE, THIS IS HOLY
GROUND.
This is holy ground. Ah Jesus, YOU ARE
OH MY GOOD
ATMOSPHERE.
HALLELUJAH.
WHY? YOU BROUGHT THE SPIRIT. IF THE MAN
IS IN THE FLESH, YOU CAN'T CONNECT.
IF THE MAN IS AFTER YOUR BODY, HE CAN'T
SEE IT. THE ATMOSPHERE IS DIFFERENT.
SEE, intimidation capacity.
Am I speaking to anyone? This is the
alignment in the spirit [music]
because the moment the spirit influences
the soul. The flesh is under the control
and this is HOW WE OVERCOME THE FLESH.
THAT'S WHY WE NEED TO GIVE ATTENTION TO
the [music] spirit. Prayer put makeup
here. Let me tell YOU THE MOMENT YOU are
beautiful here this thing will fall in
place. WE DON'T DEAL WITH YOU ACCORDING
TO FACE VALUE. AFTER 5 MINUTES I'LL BE
USED TO YOUR FACE. THE NEXT THING WILL
BE WHAT CARRIES THOU? WE DON'T CONNECT
WITH YOU BECAUSE OF YOUR BODY SIZE. YOU
CAN BE SHORT BUT ANOINTED. You can be
big and full of the Holy Ghost. SO IT IS
NOT ABOUT HOW THE BODY LOOKS LIKE. IT IS
ABOUT THE POSSIBILITIES OF THE SPIRIT.
AND THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO INVEST HERE.
Show me a man that has invested
spiritually and is depressed.
JOY DOES NOT COME FROM HERE. This one
needs happenings and happiness. Praise
happening.
HAPPEN
ATMOSPHERE
after happening.
So you need
you need another happening and this is
where we miss it. So we try to create
church to be a place of happenings not
encounters
not encounters. And that's why we are
raising very weak defeated believers.
The day you will be in a position to
praise in a storm. No, you are not
maturing. That you have denied the
devil. You are telling him you can touch
my soul. You can touch my body, but you
can't touch the conduit of my fellowship
with my master.
That's why the story of Job is there is
to show you a man that conquered but he
was a spirit man. He refused to live in
the realities. Guess what? The flesh was
well pumpered. The Bible says Job used
to wash his feet in butter.
Okay. Sometimes I read the Bible like
THAT JUST FOR THE IMAGE TO BE REAL AND
BUTTER WAS FOR THE RICH. IT WAS NOT AS
available as it is today. And that was
to show you how the flesh was well taken
care of. The man was considered to be
the [music] wealthiest. He moved from
the rank of a city millionaire to a
beggar in the street. But never cast
God.
Never cast God because the first thing
you met in Job was his spirit. Not the
achievements
of the not the achievements that are
connected to the flesh. Let me land this
person. Have you seen how you ought to
be? Are you getting it? Yesterday I was
in a meeting. It was a graduation.
As I was sitted there, I said, "These
guys have written pastor there in the
program." And you know, graduation it
began well. There was a lot of joy. How
you know the gradu was brought. They
were singing and I was feeling wow. You
know, and I began to look at my Bible.
When you see a pastor in church going
through his Bible, he's changing his
sermon. He's feeling
deep.
So I began to look. The Holy Ghost told
me, "What is the name on that flyer?"
Pastor, how did they receive you? Pastor
told me, "Show up in your office." H.
So the meeting almost went up. The Holy
Ghost came up and I could tell happen
something happened and I say there was
an option for me to come as a pastor and
there was an option for me to come as a
spirit man to do what the spirit wanted
me to do.
Are you getting me? And let me tell you
the concept of fitting in most of the
times is when you send the flesh ahead
of the spirit. I said where they call me
as a pastor I'll do pastoral work. I
will pray and teach the word and sit
down. The [music] spirit has to be in
front. Tell your neighbor neighbor this
how you go for dates.
This is how you go for company meetings.
This is how you go for deals. Are we
together? You show up in a meeting and
discernment tells you wrong deal and you
listen to the guy and he's mentioning
money to star your appetite but
appetites are here you deal with
discernment
you know s we can make 100 million but
you see we
red flag
you've never made 100 million and you
tell them give me time I want to think
about Holy
Ghost, cover me with your wings. Take
away this appetite. Every door that is
not mine, close it. And you tell the
guy, I'm sorry, we can't do business.
I'm sorry, but
Watch your flesh is of a consequence
appetite.
Hallelujah. So this is the order. Are
you getting me? I'm staying there
because I'm sorting someone. I I said
I'll take time. Now this is the soul.
This is what the devil FIGHTS FOR. YOUR
MIND IS HERE. YOUR MIND IS HERE and I'm
going to give you the few things that
are in the mind then we leave. Have you
learned something? You can have your
seats. Let me share the few things that
are in the mind.
Your mind has two components. Your mind
has two components. I'm sharing this
then we pray and leave. Is that okay?
So if you know anyone that is depressed,
oppressed, tell them to follow this
series.
And I'm also planning to duplicate this
into a book. Your mind has two
component. The first component has what
I call intellect stroke logic or/logic.
There is a part of your mind that
carries the intellect and the logic.
There is a part that carries emotions
and there is a part that carries will,
self-will. So there is intellect,
emotions and
will. WE ALWAYS SAY NOT MY WILL but your
will.
THE ONLY WAY YOU CAN deal with the will
of God and the capacity to surrender
your will is when you change what you
know and what you feel. Allow me to
explain this intellect. As I'm speaking
right now, I'm not speaking to your
spirit. I am depositing data in your
intellect capacity. There there IS
SOMETHING IN YOUR MIND THAT FEEDS ON
KNOWLEDGE.
It is there WHETHER GOOD OR BAD
KNOWLEDGE THERE IS SOMETHING THAT FEEDS
ON KNOWLEDGE. It is in the mind. THAT'S
WHY WE GO to school to feed the
intellect.
And everyone has emotions. It is called
the seat of emotion. The seat of
emotion.
And for me the will or the gate of will.
This is the actions we do or the actions
we take.
OUR ACTIONS ARE DICTATED by what we know
and what we feel. That's what dictate
OUR ACTIONS. YOU CAN'T CHANGE WHAT A MAN
DOES [music] until you change what a man
knows and what he feels. That's the
reality. THIS IS THE LECTURES THAT
PEOPLE ARE GIVEN even in rehabs. BECAUSE
IF I TELL YOU ALCOHOL IS SWEET AND WHEN
YOU GET HIGH YOU SPEAK ENGLISH, I've
started something.
Are we together? AND IF I TELL YOU WHEN
YOU ARE STRESSED UP, ALCOHOL WILL HELP
YOU. One day you'll be stressed up. You
will take alcohol because you have a
knowledge and you felt like a good
example is a story of Adam and Eve. Eve,
the devil visits Eve. And there's a
reason why Eve was visited and not Adam.
The reason is very simple. God spoke to
Adam. Adam spoke to Eve. Now,
Adam had God. Eve had Adam. Let me show
you the order. WHEN YOU HEAR GOD, IT IS
REVELATION. WHEN YOU HEAR MAN, IT IS
INFORMATION. NOW, A MAN THAT HAS
REVELATION CARRIES CONVICTION.
A MAN THAT CARRIES INFORMATION CARRIES
UNDERSTANDING.
OKAY, I'm coming TO YOU. SO, WHEN I HEAR
GOD, I CARRY CONVICTION. YOU CAN'T TAKE
ME OUT. If I sleep and I hear God like
I've had God 2022 Mikuama, you can't
change my mind. You can give me budgets
but you can't change MY CONVICTION. I
KNOW THAT I KNOW I'VE heard God.
[snorts] Are we TOGETHER NOW? MEN THAT
HEAR GOD CARRY CONVICTION. SEE HOW THE
DEVIL APPROACHED EVE? THE DEVIL CAME AND
SAID, "Did God really say really say?
Are you sure you had God
those days IN FOR ONE?
GO AND TELL FROM FALSE FORCE to shut up
FOR FALSE THE PRINCIPAL HAS SAID YOU
SHUT UP. YOU KNOW THAT TIME YOU ARE NOT
AFRAID. YOU KNOW THE SOURCE THAT HAS
SENT YOU NOW
to shut up.
Are you sure YOU HAVE? SO AT THAT LEVEL
YOUR CONFIDENCE IS ALTERED. ARE you
getting me? So ideally Eve became the
RIGHT CANDIDATE. NOW WHAT DID EVE
RECEIVE INFORMATION? WHAT WAS ABSENT
EXPLANATION?
SO THE LAW SAID THOU SHALT NOT EAT. EVE
ANSWERED AND said even touch said right
candidate. Did God really say? WE WERE
TOLD NOT to eat or even touch. With who?
Okay. DO YOU KNOW NOW THAT ONE DO YOU
KNOW IS EXPLANATION? WHAT DOES
EXPLANATION STAR? CURIOSITY.
SOME OF US WE WERE GOOD UNTIL
EXPLANATION CAME.
MY FIRST KISS WILL BE ON THE ALTAR.
The frogs you have kissed.
Now what happened WHEN YOU WHEN YOU ARE
INNOCENT MAKING THAT VOW?
You had information then someone BROUGHT
EXPLANATION.
AND THAT EXPLANATION CAME with added
information.
SO YOU SEE ALREADY THAT INTELLECT,
LOGIC, FACULTY ATTRACTED another data
that was conflicting.
AND EVERY WORD CARRIES some energy.
WORDS ARE NOT SYLLABLES. WORDS ARE
ENERGIES.
THAT IS WHY
silence sometimes can never be
offensive.
WORDS, ONE WORD TODAY, ONE WORD. I CAN
WALK OUT here and look at you and say,
"Wow, you look amazing." The favor of
God is upon you, Jesus. And we'll go
home feeling.
Why? I've just uttered words. THE ENERGY
IN THAT WORD HAS SHIFTED your energy
levels emotionally.
and the next thing you came happy but
you're going TO LEAVE SIR WHY I'VE NOT
BEATEN YOU I'VE released an energy from
words that are negative am I speaking to
anyone are you getting IT AND THAT'S WHY
THAT FACULTY OF INTELLECT and logic is
always crying for information,
knowledge.
And when it is filled with the wrong
information, it will begin to control
how you feel.
AND THE MOMENT YOUR KNOWLEDGE AND YOUR
EMOTIONS
ARE UNDER CERTAIN POWER, YOUR ACTIONS
will be automatically off because your
will is different. NOW SEE HOW GOD
CHANGES US. GOD WILL RELEASE revelation
to take charge of intellect. GOD WILL
GIVE YOU THE HOLY GHOST TO TAKE CHARGE
of your emotions. THE MOMENT YOU HAVE
THE REVELATION of God and the emotions
of the Holy Ghost, you will do the will
of the father.
Hello.
Am I speaking to anyone? SO WHAT WE HAVE
DENIED PEOPLE IS THE TRUTH OF THE FATHER
and the encounters of the spirit. AND SO
WE WE HAVE PEOPLE THAT ARE STRUGGLING to
obey the will of God. IT IS WHEN THE CRY
OF THE SPIRIT BECOMES YOUR CRY. THE
FEELINGS OF THE HOLY GHOST BECOMES YOUR
FEELINGS. And it is WHEN THE KNOWLEDGE
OF GOD RULETH YOUR MIND THAT YOU WILL DO
THINGS ACCORDING to the will of God.
I met a young girl and she told me,
"Pass,
I'm in this relationship. It's not good
and I want to get out, but I don't want
to hurt the guy." I said, "No, there are
two guys in this picture. There is Jesus
and Kenovia.
At the end of the day, one will be hurt.
Choose to hurt Kenovia or Jesus. I said
the matter is heavy in your court
because you keep this guy because of
indulgence. Jesus is bleeding. If you
leave this guy, Jesus who's your creator
will be happy. So Kenovia cannot give
you Jesus but Jesus can give you another
Kenovia. Make your decisions
wisely. Hallelujah. Am I speaking to
anyone? The second faculty.
So, so you have seen that faculty. Okay?
That's why we teach the word every day
cuz you can never change the life of a
man until you change what they know. Men
are product of knowledge. And that's why
you see right now the rate of atheism is
high because secular intelligence is
also on the rise. So people have a
knowing that is not of God and then now
they tend to incline that knowledge also
carries energies and emotions. The
second one is the second faculty of your
mind carries consciousness,
subconsciousness and memory.
It carries consciousness,
subconsciousness and memory. Excuse me.
Sorry. It carries consciousness,
subconsciousness and memory. Now, let me
tell you some of the people that
struggle in their mind is because of
memories. You have a flash disc for lack
of a better word. You have a memory
stick. Some of you is 250 GB full of
garbage,
BAD EXPERIENCES. THE LORD MUST FLUSH IT.
ALL THE THINGS OF YOUR LIFE, NEGATIVE,
NEGATIVE, NEGATIVE. NO GOOD ENCOUNTERS.
Allow me to say this. And this one I'm
preparing for the singles in August. One
of the things you need to do before you
get married is interrogate the baggage
of background. Everyone has a
background. You get a man who was raised
by a single mother. That man has daddy
hunger. You get a woman who was raised
by a single mother. She has survival
tactics without a man.
She has seen her mother survive without
a man. So don't think you will come and
see whether you are going to control. So
that's a baggage. See people she has
lived. Her memories are surviving
without a man. So who are you to think
that she will not live? So some ladies
are not bad. You must when you receive a
woman, choose your problems wisely.
That's why you DID TO ANALYZE YOUR
PROBLEM and say this problem is
manageable.
Hallelujah.
I'M SPEAKING FACTS. THERE IS NO PERFECT
MAN, NO PERFECT WOMAN. WE NO ONE CAME
FROM HEAVEN. WE ARE ALL FROM SYSTEMS
that shaped how we view things. SO BY
THE TIME SHE SHOWS UP OR HE shows up,
YOU YOU GET A MAN WHOSE FATHER used to
be commanding and dominating. He gets in
the house and says nakami. He could be
speaking in tongues, but he has a
baggage of command. And you were raised
where your father used to go to the
kitchen and do dishes. Now you have
married. That is a time bomb.
I know I'm dealing with stuff. It's
called burden of background. Tell your
neighbor neighbor when you are dirty
collect data
upis hypothesis. ANALYZE
A RED FLAG. DON'T IGNORE.
The day you stand here, it will be too
late because even if you leave the guy,
you are still in the covenant. So we
must understand this thing. Yes. Yes.
Everyone has a background. Some of us
were raised in boy schools.
Some grew in mixed schools. So raised
boy school.
My wife used to tell me
I'm realizing
forehead.
Lack of prayer
boy school FROM
thought we are going to meet.
Hallelujah.
It [snorts] will be a nice conversation.
Amen. Because I've discovered some of
these things are elementary, but people
don't. People ignore them. We've put a
lot of pressure on a woman who loves
God, a woman who prays, a woman who your
intercessor. Proverbs 31 will have a
real conversation. You'll know that
everyone is made even you before you
become that man or woman. We are
finishing. Amen. So tell your neighbor
this memory, subconsciousness,
and consciousness.
Consciousness is the reality of the now.
Subconscious is when you cannot
recognize the [music] now.
When a man faints, he enters
subconscious. When you sleep, the
subconscious memory is the dealings that
are stored in a certain archive in the
mind. Are we together? Are we together?
Also in the soul. So these are the
things that constitute the soul. The
soul also has senses. The five senses.
Smell, see, touch, [music] taste, and
hear. The soul has all that. So you can
see the big part of the soul constitute
the mind. Are we together? The big part
of the soul constitutes the mind. And
that's why
he that has your mind has your life
automatically.
And a wise man wrote and said never lose
your mind. You might lead it in the next
relationship.
So don't lose your mind. Are we
together? Let me give you the biblical
definition of the mind and the
psychological so that you can be at par
with the people of the first service.
Nepes. The bibilical the word nepesh is
a Hebrew word. Nehe [music]
is what it means. Soul or mind in
Hebrew. And nepesh has five meanings.
Nepes or nephesh has five meanings.
The first meaning it means person.
Person it means person. The second one
it means soul. It means soul. The third
one it means appetite. [music]
It means appetite. The fourth one it
means life. And the fifth one it means
you. It means you or the real you. So
the mind is nephesh. In Hebrew it means
life, soul, appetite, person and you.
Are we together? So when the Bible talks
about the mind, it automatically talks
about your life, your soul, your
appetite, your person and the real you.
That is why the battle of the mind will
always attack the whole of you. The
psychological one is a little bit
technical. I don't know does someone
need that definition? Yes. Okay. for
learners. This one has many jagons. The
psychological definition of the mind uh
is the aspect of intellect.
The aspect of intellect. The aspect of
intellect and consciousness.
The aspect of intellect and
consciousness manifested
manifested
as combination
of thought
manifested as combination of thoughts,
perceptions.
Thoughts, perceptions,
memory,
emotions.
Thoughts, perceptions,
memory, emotions, will
and imagination.
Will and imagination.
including all of the brain. Including
all of the brain's
consciousness
and unconscious cognitive process,
including all of the brain's
consciousness,
all of the brain's [music] consciousness
and unconscious
all of the brains consciousness and
unconscious cognitive process. The
psychological definition of the mind
touches on all the elements of the mind.
It touches on the memory, the
consciousness, the will, the emotions.
Let me give you
this is something for those of you that
have brothers,
anyone in addiction.
This is what I call the hierarchy of
change. Write it down. The hierarchy of
change. The hierarchy of change.
The hierarchy of change. You begin with
knowledge. Number one. You don't change
a behavior without addressing what the
person knows. You don't change a
behavior without addressing what the
person knows. So you begin with
knowledge. That knowledge will produce
these six things. I believe knowledge
will number one change your perception.
Perception. Perception. Perception is
the view in [music] judgment of
something. If I tell you this water is
not good for human consumption, how you
will view this glass, it will not be
attractive. But if I tell you this water
is very sweet, how you view it, it will
be different. Why? Because the knowledge
changes how you view the glass. Are we
together? The second thing after
perception is changed your attitude is
altered. Attitude. attitude
attitude
the dealings
you you you will see it as poison but
even as you pass here you'll not even
bother with it you know this is a bad
thing you can even hold it and pour it
so that someone does not take if I say
it is sweet you might pass here look at
the water look at the people and
something will tell you why your
attitude towards the thing if a child
shakes the table you'll tell them that's
a good thing are we Father, when
attitude is changed, it begins to
trigger our habits. Our habits, whatever
you do, a habit is a projection of your
attitude. Is a projection of your
attitude. There's a book I was reading
was called the seven habits of
successful men and even the writings of
Miles Monroe. He dwells a lot with
attitude because he said the results of
men are connected to attitude. Your
attitude of life determines how far you
go in life. If you have a wrong attitude
and that attitude has a background of
information. Are we together? So now
that will uh affect your habit what you
do and a repeated habit becomes a
behavior. A repeated habit becomes a
behavior. And a repeated behavior
becomes a lifestyle. And a repeated
lifestyle shapes your destiny.
So out of that hierarchy you see if we
don't release knowledge we are already
affecting destiny because men will live
uphazardly. So the entrance of knowledge
aligns so many things. Are we together?
Are we together? Now when there is
entrance of wrong knowledge something is
introduced. When you have wrong
knowledge like what Eve received
explanation
her perception about the fruit changed
her attitude changed and something got
introduced is called curiosity.
Curiosity and that is what made Eve pick
the fruit. Now see the coordination
there is knowledge, explanation,
perception, attitude. Then what is did
did she do? First of all, the five
[music] senses were involved. She saw,
she touched, she smelled, she tasted
because she heard.
Okay, I repeat. She heard the voice
sense of hearing. It changed how she
saw. Curiosity provoked her to pick that
is touch. Before you eat, you must have
smelled. Then eating is the concept of
taste. So you can see how the soul
becomes very important when it comes to
the attacks of the devil. Am I speaking
to anyone? So because we are a church of
young people, I know sometimes
Saturday church we're doing a good job
and most of the times when people come
to report matters to us especially when
you're pastoring a young church it is
not an opportunity to kill
are you getting it because there is a
reason why that person is doing what
they are interrogate the what I call the
vacancy of knowledge and train them
that's That's why many young people
don't relate with church.
So the the point there is discredit the
ministry
kick the boy out but who has the time to
sit with him and know the knowledge come
are we together and that's WHY IT'S NOT
EASY because you have to sit. SO IF
TODAY SOMEONE COMES AND TELLS ME
the easiest thing is to tell them
the next thing is to be intentional and
tell them the altar and righteousness
and teach them and I tell you it is more
beneficial to train a man and give the
right knowledge than to kick them out
and that's what many churches are doing.
We are not sitting men down to tell
them. It's like we are waiting for
perfect men that we never raise.
It doesn't happen like that. Ministry is
about carrying the errors and the soils
of men. By the time they call you
And I say that is the price of
fatherhood.
So we have even in the spirit we have to
pay the price. And that's why I rather
sit you down like this take you poly
poly bit by bit precept by precept so
that the day I will rebuke you I'll have
authority.
That is not in your level. You are
better than this. grow up and I love you
and I hug you and I tell you seven days
go and repenttor
I want you to pray for me
1 to three days
I'm training you to survive without my
presence because if I don't do that you
will never grow but I believe Aloma she
was traveling amen let's stand up on our
feet thank you Holy Ghost I just want us
to make a prayer
now we understand better are we together
and this is the prayer that I want you
to make I've talked about the flesh and
I've taught about the soul I just want
you to tell the Holy Ghost to strengthen
you in the inner man your battles in
life are connected to the body and the
soul
In just 2 minutes, call upon the
heavens.
It is prayers of understanding that
bring clarity.
Just tell the Lord, Lord, strengthen me
in my spirit so that I can be able to
subdue the flesh. Listen to me. The
appetites of the flesh sometimes are too
strong. The urges and the desires are
too powerful. But I want to assure you,
the Holy Spirit is not limited. HE'S NOT
INCAPACITATED. HE HAS THE POWER. I TELL
YOU, WE WILL SEE A RUSSIA'S CHURCH. WE
WILL SEE YOUNG MEN THOUGH THEY IN THIS
REALM, THEY ARE SAINTS. THEY HAVE BEEN
SET APART. THEY ARE HAGGOS. THEY HAVE
BEEN CONSECRATED. They carry the
proclivities of the Holy Ghost. IT IS BY
THIS UNDERSTANDING THAT YOU begin to
TELL THE LORD, "EVERY MEMORY, LET IT BE
DELETED. WHATEVER WAS PLANTED IN MY
MIND, ENCOUNTERS AND EVENTS THAT
HAPPENED IN MY LIFE THAT BEGAN TO SHAPE
MY DESTINY, LET THEM BE DELETED TODAY.
LET them be deleted today. THIS IS THE
HOUR TO TELL THE LORD, "FILL MY MIND
WITH THY WORD. LET THY WORD OCCUPY EVERY
AREA AND EVERY SECT OF MY MIND." SOME OF
US, WE STRUGGLE WITH THOUGHTS. WE
STRUGGLE WITH PATTERNS OF IDEOLOGIES.
THEY ARE DEMONIC. WHEN GOD BREATHED, HE
THAT WAS A FRESH BREATH. THE FIRST MIND
THAT MAN CARRIED WAS A SUPERNATURAL
MIND. THAT IS WHY GOD ENTRUSTED ADAM
WITH THE ASSIGNMENT OF NAMING ALL THE
ANIMALS. BEGIN TO DECLARE, "LET THE
ORIGINAL BREATH OF GOD BE UPON MY LIFE.
LET THE HOLY GHOST TAKE CHARGE OF MY
EMOTIONS. I WANT TO OPERATE IN THE WILL
OF ELLEON. I WANT TO WALK IN THE
ORDINANCES OF ELLEON. LET THE SPIRIT OF
GOD, LET HIM TAKE CHARGE OF MY EMOTIONS.
LET THE WORD OF GOD, LET IT delete and
replace ANYTHING THAT STOOD AS A TRUTH."
THE BIBLE SAID, "YOUR WORD IS LIFE AND
YOUR WORD IS LIGHT." LET THE LIFE OF THE
WORD BEGIN TO TAKE PREEMINENCE IN MY
MIND. LET THE LIFE OF THAT WORD, LET IT
TAKE CHARGE OF MY LIFE. THE BIBLE
DECLARES THAT THE GOSPEL IS THE POWER
UNTO SALVATION. LET THE POWER RESIDENT
IN THE GOSPEL NOW DELIVER ME AND SET ME
FREE.
MY SOUL, MY SOUL, LET THERE BE AN
INTERROGATION. EVERYTHING THAT IS NOT OF
THE LORD. IT WAS DAVID THAT CAME TO A
PLACE AND SAID, "SEARCH MY HEART. SEARCH
MY NE, SEARCH MY SOUL, OH GOD. LET THIS
BE A DAY. LET THE LORD INTERROGATE EVERY
SOUL. LET THE LORD SEARCH EVERY SOUL.
THEIR DESIRES, THEIR APPETITES, [music]
their things deposited. LET THERE BE A
DIVINE DELAY.
MAY I BE ALIVE IN THE SPIRIT. MAY I BE
ALIVE IN THE SPIRIT. MAY I BE AWAKE IN
THE SPIRIT.
LET MY SPIRIT BE STRENGTHENED. I RECEIVE
STRENGTH IN THE INNER MAN. I RECEIVE
STRENGTH IN THE INNER MAN. I AM AN
OVERCOMER. I AM VICTORIOUS. I'M MORE
THAN A CONQUEROR. THE FLESH SHALL NOT
RULE ME. THE SOUL SHALL NOT RULE ME. I
AM A SPIRIT MAN. I WALK BY THE DICKNESS
OF THE SPIRIT. I AM ORDAINED FROM ABOVE.
EVERY BATTLE OF THE FLESH, EVERY BATTLE
OF THE SOUL, LET IT END RIGHT NOW IN THE
MIGHTY NAME OF JESUS. LET YOUR
CONSCIOUS, YOUR SUBCONSCIOUS [music]
AND MEMORY, LET THEM BE RENEWED BY THE
WORD. LET THY INTELLECT, LET THE DEPOSIT
OF LIES, LET THEM BE DELETED. MEMORIES
THAT KEEP ON HAUNTING YOU, LET THEM BE
DELETED TODAY IN THE MIGHTY NAME OF
JESUS.
Let the mind of Christ be with you. THAT
MIND THAT WAS IN JESUS, let it be upon
you. Hallelujah.
As we prepare to give our offering,
when God breathed upon Adam, it was a
fresh breath.
The man received a supernatural mind.
There is a level of supernatural
thinkings. That possibility is still
there. That's why the Bible says, "Be ye
renewed."
Be ye renewed. Be ye metamophos.
There's something called the renewing of
the mind. It's taking the mind back to
its original status. Some of us, we have
international
ideas. They cannot be handled in this
realm. There is a mind. Jesus said, "Let
this mind," Paul writes and says, "Let
this mind that was in Christ be in you."
What does that mean? I have to permit
that mind. The word let there is permit.
Allow the expression [music] of the
thought patterns of Jesus to be upon
you. Begin to see things with the lenses
of Elleon. Don't see them from a
defeated level. Begin to see matters in
the level of Christ. There is a mindset
that is of God. That mind can never be
depressed. That is the mind that says
where there is a casting down, you begin
to declare a lifting up. It looks like
it is confessing contrally. But those
are the realities of where we live.
There are atmospheres that are negative.
There is a level you reach and you have
to come to a place and encourage
yourself because atmospheres are too
defeating. There are levels you enter
and everything is crumbling down.
Hello. Next Sunday we'll launch out on
it. And some of us, let me say this, I
discovered one thing and this one I'm
saying with a lot of wisdom. will build
it up next Sunday. There are there are
men that act as gates to your mind.
You see where I am as a pastor. Not
everyone can reach me, but there are
people that can be reached. This is what
I've learned to do. Elijah, anyone that
comes to tell me something, I always
audit because I know you could be a
Peter who's telling me don't go to the
cross. You are very close. So the devil
knows I can't speak to pastor T d d d d
d d d d d d d d d d d d d d d d dly, but
I'm going to use a Peter to pass the
communication. Listen to [music] me.
Some gossips blow to your door. They are
coming as a pathway to disrupt your
mental function.
Be wise. Audit everyone that comes with
stories.
Let me give you wisdom. Go and audit
some people who bring you news and ask
yourself out of 10 news, how many are
positive?
The moment you discover
gossip number one
gossip number two you look at 10 of them
negative that's not a friend that's a
gate that's a gate OF TORMENTATION THAT
YOU ARE VERY JOYFUL AND THEN THEY look
for you and they begin to poison and you
discover after that you feel like you
are drained some of these things are
dates I'll teach about gossip on Sunday.
Gossip is like fire. It spreads where
people talk. It stops when a man keeps
quiet. You must be the diffuse of
gossip.
Are you getting it? AND SOME OF US, YOU
BEGIN THE DAY SO WELL AND THE DEVIL
KNOWS THIS one will never fornicate.
This one will never drink. But I know
I'll attack the soul.
I don't
tell your neighbor, neighbor, there are
some gossipers who are losing audience
today.
They affect you.
May you be delivered from those doors.
Your life must be full of joy and full
of happiness. from today be alert when
gossip doors and and these are men very
close to you. So
sell
father I bless your sons and daughters
and dear Lord I declare
that this coming week shall be the best
for them. I declare possibilities of
Zion. I declare doors are opening. Iron
gates, bronze gates where everything
ordained for them in this coming week
shall locate them. As they are stepping
out, they [music] are stepping out to
manifest and shine. We are in this body
to rule. We declare dominion is our
nature. As we are stepping out, we have
authority. Dominion over the air,
dominion over the land and over the sea.
No power of darkness can hinder us and
stop us. I declare these are the lights
set up on high places. They are shining
and radiating with the glory of Elleon.
May this be the best week of your life.
May this be a week [music] of
testimonies. May this be a week to
declare the goodness of the Lord in the
land of the living. May this be a week
of eleation and divine encounters. May
this be a week to journey IN THE SPIRIT
AND DISCOVER DESTINATIONS IN the realm
of the SPIRIT AS WE STEP OUT EVEN THE
NEW WAVE OF CO CANNOT TOUCH YOU. I
COVENANT WITH YOUR LIFE, COVENANT WITH
YOUR DESTINY, COVENANT WITH YOUR FUTURE
AND I DECLARE YOU ARE COVERED. YOU
CANNOT BE SICK. THAT VIRUS HAS NO
PERMISSION TO TOUCH you in the name of
Jesus. Whatever you do shall prosper.
Where you lay your hands shall succeed.
where God has planted you, your grace
will flow in Jesus name we pray.
For all the parents when you take your
children, we wish you journey masses and
we have prayed for your sons and
daughters. They are the best.
Hallelujah. They are the best. They will
bring you honor. Amen. Before I receive
the offering, is there anyone I've seen
visitors? Visitors we are meeting at the
VIP parala. Amen. Hallelujah. If you're
a visitor, don't worry. We have capino
and pizza. Today we're doing cappuccino.
Today's day for mocha. Okay. Well, I I
think it will be there. Amen. By faith.
Underline the word faith. Amen. Is there
anyone that wants to receive Jesus?
Amen. This is the best offering that you
can give. Anyone? Anyone?
You know there are people who come to
church accept.
So I wouldn't like to lock anyone out.
Hallelujah. Okay. Are you ready to give?
Oh, thank you. Yes. Let's receive that
brother. Thank you. Just a Hashim here.
Hashame here. Come, bro. Come.
Amen. Let's celebrate. My goodness. My
goodness. Amen.
Amen.
God, I could bless. Thank you for
coming. Is there anyone else?
Just begin to pray for him. Anyone else?
You know, I just like it when I see men
come to the Lord and even women without
a song. Just a conviction of the spirit.
Hallelujah. Is there anyone else you're
there? Listen, we we can wait for you
for 2 minutes. This is very important.
More than the offering we are
collecting, this is very important. Is
there anyone else? Anyone else? My
goodness. You know some of us our
parents have been crying for us. So
coming to the Lord is very powerful. Is
there anyone else? Jesus.
[music]
Amen. Let's just stretch our hands and
pray for this brother. This day is the
day that the Lord had made for him.
Begin to pray. This is a soul. This is a
destiny. This is a life. This is a man
that carries the possibilities of Zion.
Before the foundations of the earth, the
Lord knew you. You are ordained for
greatness. You are not an accident. You
are not a mistake. You are a child of
God. You carry the image of the father.
You carry the nature of your father.
Today is the day to surrender your soul
to the possibilities [music]
and the REALITIES OF ZION, KNOWING that
you cannot save yourself. YOU HAVE RUN
TO THE ALTAR BELIEVING THAT HE DIED for
you, he delivered you. AND NOW I DECLARE
BY THE AUTHORITY THAT IS IN THE NAME OF
JESUS, THE BIBLE SAYS THEM THAT
BELIEVED, HE GAVE THEM THE POWER TO
BECOME THE SONS OF GOD, YOU ARE A CHILD
OF GOD. BEHOLD, THE OLD IS GONE AND THE
NEW HAS COME. THERE IS NOW NO
CONDEMNATION TO THEM THAT ARE IN CHRIST
JESUS. MAY THIS MARK AS a new DAY IN
YOUR LIFE. A new beginning, A NEW ORDER
HAS JUST BEGUN. MAY THE HOLY GHOST EVEN
COME UPON YOU TO LEAD YOU, USHER YOU,
CONTROL YOU, AND GOVERN YOUR LIFE IN THE
NAME OF JESUS. WHATEVER YOU DID IN THE
PAST IS IN THE PAST. YOU ARE NOW
STEPPING INTO A NEW YOU, STEPPING INTO A
NEW TRUTH, STEPPING INTO A NEW REALITY.
In the name of Jesus, I want you to
repeat this prayer after me. The Bible
says when you believe in your heart and
confess with your mouth that Jesus is
Lord, that indeed uh that will make you
you you there is a conversion that
happens. It is not the prayer that
saves. It is the belief that saves.
Amen. Just say Lord Jesus today
willingly I come to you knowing that I'm
a sinner in need of a savior. I accept I
cannot save myself. I accept you died
for my sins. You resurrected to give me
a better resurrection. And today I
confess with my mouth because I believe
in my heart that Jesus is Lord. And I
declare now I'm a new man. I'M BORN
AGAIN. BORN OF GOD, BORN OF THE SPIRIT.
AND I belong to you Jesus. WHEN YOU COME
FOR THE CHURCH, let me be among the
bride in Jesus name. Wow. Hallelujah.
Church, let's celebrate our brother.
Let's celebrate him. Hallelujah.
Hallelujah.
What's your name, sir?
I'm Steve. Yes. Steve.
Steve.
God. S. This is a good man. is going to
take your name.
Amen. Wow. Let's celebrate Steve.
Hallelujah.
Amen. Jesus is Lord.
If Jesus can save, he can heal. Amen.
That's how you know Jesus is in the
house because no one comes unto the
father unless called by the son. Did you
come with your offering and your tithe
and your first fruit and your will give
it? It's time to give. Tell your
neighbor now let's give. Tell your
neighbor, let's give. Amen. Let me tell
you something, church. Even as we are
giving, if all of us, if all of us were
faithful with their tithes and
offerings, the word is faithful. Are you
getting it? If all of us are faithful
with their tithes, offerings, the free
will we are giving. I tell you the
truth, we don't need to raise money in
another way. tithe offering and your
pledges those who pledged that's hold on
yesterday we did an event for young
people it was a little bit expensive and
I said if all of us are faithful we will
we don't even need to have I don't know
a special contribution because men are
meeting the church will have capacity to
run every event without pain and I want
us to adopt that culture that you are
just saying I'm faithful are we together
with my tithe and my offer
A conference is coming up and I want to
assure you we don't need to do a
fundraiser. We don't need people to
pledge.
The money you give and that's how you
become partakers of blessing because the
moment that money goes to the works of
ministry. Yesterday some young men came
here they were filled with the Holy
Ghost. We spent almost 50,000 just to
have an event. Let me tell you, you
can't compare that destiny with 50,000.
And we couldn't charge them because we
know they are the mercies of parents. Is
that okay? So the moment we are just
faithful, tell your neighbor faithful.
Tell your neighbor faithful. Tell your
neighbor that we will do many things.
Are we together? And and that will be my
word to you. I know we don't I don't
call people. I don't even know how much
you tithe. There are places where if you
don't t
You know, we don't do that. Amen.
Because I really want to get you to give
out of revelation. There are many
projects ahead of us. Even the whole
moving, we need a lot of money. But I
want to believe these people here are
sufficient to carry the burden. Is that
okay? Yes. I know we uh there are times
God will speak to you and command you to
give a seed. Will be willing to receive.
But one thing I'll never do, I'll never
lie to you knowing that I have a need. I
rather come and tell you
to
but God has been faithful. So the giving
details are there. Father bless your
sons and daughters. We give because we
love you. The Bible says them that love
you obey your word. We give because we
are in obedience with your word. the
different portions, the 10%, the first
fruit, the free will giving, the
instructed seeds, whatever they are, oh
God, we are laying it on your altar
because we know this altar has fed us.
This altar has empowered us and we know
that there are demands in your house. We
are giving so that the storehouse can
never lack. And dear Lord, we pray as we
connect whatever activity happens. May
we [music] be partakers. As Paul prayed
and said, "May my God supply all your
needs according to his riches in glory."
I declare may the same blessing be upon
every giver today in Jesus mighty name.
And now the grace of our Lord Jesus
Christ and the love of God and the
fellowship of the Holy Spirit be with us
now and forever more. Amen. We have
pastor Senate's pre-wedding. Uh possibly
if you are leaving, you can take an
envelope, put the money there and put
pastor Senate pre-wedding. Is that okay?
So that at least
we are okay. So God bless you and have
the best week possible. I have taken my
45 minutes and I want to assure you I've
not even spent any more time. That was
my 45 minutes. God bless you.
Where?
Where
[music]
anywhere? [singing]
[singing]
Where? Anyway,
we [music] will.
Hallelujah.
Say my
[singing and music]
hallelujah.
[music]